准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
蟹堡恐惧症
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
编剧
技术总监
动画总监
制片指导
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
蟹堡王
总算画完了
Finished at last
你们说我的大作怎么样
What do you boys think of me masterpiece?
新营业时间
早上七点到晚上十一点
什么
What?
也太过分了吧
That is totally unfair
章鱼哥说得对  太过分了
Squidward's right, that's totally unfair
就不能选个早于六点的上班时间吗
Couldn't we get to work earlier than 6:00 a.m.?
就比如早上五点半
Like 5:30 a.m.?
或者早上五点
Or 5:00 a.m.?
或者早上四点
Or 4:00 a.m.?
闭嘴
Zip it
什么
What the?
海之霸
现在
23小时营业
海之霸要23小时营业
The Chum Bucket open 23 hours
所以说那个小废物痞老板
So, that little piece of flotsam Plankton
以为自己营业时间能比我长是吧
thinks he can stay open longer than me, does he?
还好吧
Sure
无所谓
I don't know
又咋了
Why not?
那他就错了
Well, he's wrong
那好吧
Okay, sure
现在起   蟹堡王24小时营业
As of now, the Krusty Krab is open 24 hours
听见没  章鱼哥
Did you hear that, Squidward?
我们要一直工作工作工作
We get to keep working and working and working
再也用不着回家了
without ever having to go home
掐自己一下  我一定是在做梦
I got to pinch myself 'cause I must be dreaming
我没在做梦
Well, I'm not dreaming
24小时营业
24小时营业是吧
Open 24 hours, eh?
他果然会忍不住想要比我营业久一点
I knew he couldn't resist staying open later than me
海之霸
我的邪恶大计进行得太顺利了
My evil plan is working perfectly
他会把他的员工累垮
He'll run his employees into the ground
等到海绵宝宝累到神志不清了
and when SpongeBob's mind
finally cracks from exhaustion
我就能让他告诉我蟹黄堡秘方了
I'll get him to tell me the secret Krabby Patty formula
你怎么不笑
Why aren't you laughing?
这笑话我早听过了
I've heard this joke before
蟹堡王
大家听好了
All right, everybody
蟹堡王现在已经第三天不间断服务了
The Krusty Krab is entering
day three of nonstop service
鼓掌欢庆第三天吧
Let's give it up for day three
第三天
Day three
蟹黄堡  我不在乎是不是非得营业
Krabby Patty, I don't care if we have to stay open
到世界末日之后的那一天
till the day after the end of time
但只要有你  我就圆满了
As long as I'm with you, I'm complete
第十天不间断服务
Day ten of nonstop service
蟹老板  我能回家了吗
Mr. Krabs, can I go home yet?
谁都不准回
No one goes home
你看看我的眼袋
Look at these bags under my eyes
连眼袋都有眼袋了
Even my bags have bags
别瞎抱怨了  章鱼哥
Quit your bellyaching, Squidward
你听过海绵宝宝在那瞎抱怨没
You don't hear SpongeBob complaining, do you?
我说蟹黄堡儿就是好
K-R-A-B-B-Y P-A-T-T-Y, says I
你倒是能向那小子学点东西
You can learn a few things from that boy
蟹老板  他不正常
Mr. Krabs, he is not normal
好  你可以坐下休息五分钟
All right, you can sit down for five minutes
然后继续工作
Then it's back to work
该死
Drat
还是没累垮他
He's not collapsing from exhaustion
但只要再加点压力
But with a little more pressure
海绵宝宝马上就会崩溃
the Sponge will crack like an egg
然后我就能尽情利用他破碎的心智了
Then I'll be there to feast on
the goo of his shattered psyche
蜘蛛虫
A spider bug
海之霸
快点
Now, come on
蟹堡王
Krusty Krab
不打烊的餐厅
The restaurant that never closes
你要点餐吗
You'd like to place an order?
一万份蟹黄堡
10,000 Krabby Patties?
马上就去做  这位
We'll start your order right away, Mr., uh, uh
你叫什么名字来着
What was that name again?
彼老板
Peter Lankton
等一下
Wait a minute
这该不会是恶作剧吧
This isn't some kind of prank, is it?
不会
No
好
Good
做好了就给你回电话  彼老板
We'll call you when it's ready, Mr. Lankton
全力冲刺
Kick it into high gear
大单子来了
We got a big order
我就指望你了  小子
I'm counting on you, boy
我要你举起锅铲
I need you to raise that spatular
然后我要你说  蟹堡王队加油
And I need you to say "Team Krusty Krab"
蟹堡王队加油
Team Krusty Krab
这才像话
That's me boy
快给我做一万份蟹黄堡
Now, make me 10,000 patties
不准休息
And no breaks
你听到没  锅铲
Did you hear that, spatula?
你  我
You, me
还有一万份蟹黄堡
and 10,000 Krabby Patties
而且最棒的就是
And the best part?
不准休息
No breaks
第15天
Day 15
鼓掌欢庆第15天
Give it up for day 15
我说蟹黄堡儿就是好
K-R-A-B-B-Y P-A-T-T-Y
一千三百二十
One thousand, three hundred, twenty
第23天
Day 23
鼓掌欢庆第23天
Give it up for day 23
6,654
第30天
Day 30
7,121
8,659
等等  怎么回事
Wait, what's going on?
第
Day
谁知道多少天了
Anyone know how many days it's been?
我不记得了
I lost track
四十三天
Forty-three
搞什么鬼
What the flimflam?
你在里面干什么  小子
What are you doing in here, boy?
这是在浪费我家粮食
You're wasting all me food
小子
Boy?
蟹老板
Hey, Mr. Krabs
你什么时候来的
When did you get in here?
小子  我很担心
Boy, I'm worried that
听见没
Got it?
抱歉  蟹老板
I'm sorry, Mr. Krabs
可不可以再说一遍
Could you run that by me again?
好  我之前说我很担心
Sure, I said, I'm worried that
我刚就以为你这么说的
That's what I thought you said
现在容我用这句话反驳一下
Now, let me offer this as a rebuttal
退后
Stay back
我警告你
I'm warning you
你这有点是在犯傻了
All right, now you're just acting silly
我是要你
I want you to
不要
No
别吃我
Don't eat me
我嚼不烂
I'm too chewy
见鬼了
Holy shrimp
到处都是
They're everywhere
干什么
What?
我就说那衣服太丑了吧
I told you that shirt was hideous
不要
No, no
我还不想死
I want to live
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
怎么回事
what's going on?
到处都是吃人蟹黄堡
Everywhere I look, I see killer Krabby Patties
没事了
There, there
回去工作必能解决一切问题
I'm sure it's nothing
that getting back to work won't solve
这是你的锅铲
Here's your spatular
锅铲
Spatular
这是烤架
And here's the grill
烤架
Grill
这些是新鲜蟹
And here are some fresh Krabby
果然还是有问题
There may be a problem after all
什么意思
What does this mean?
意思是你脑袋有毛病
It means there's something wrong with your head
我觉得你应该去找专业人士
Look, I think maybe you should see a professional
摔跤手吗
Wrestler?
不对
No
精神病医生
A psychiatrist
可是要上哪找精神病医生
But where am I going to find a psychiatrist
快看这个
Look at this
彼老板精神病医生
专治蟹堡恐惧症
感觉不太好吧  蟹老板
Gosh, I don't know about this, Mr. Krabs
去看医生会不会误工
Wouldn't I have to miss work if I went to see
应该就是这了
Well, this looks like the place
彼老板精神病医生
在吗
Hello?
医生
Doctor?
请进  海绵宝宝先生
Come in, Mr. SquarePants
彼老板医生
请在沙发上就座
Please, have a seat on the couch
现在
Now
来让你把有害的信息抛在脑后
let's unload all that harmful information
in your little yellow head
你比我想象的还要小啊  医生
You're a bit smaller than I imagined, Doctor
所以你才叫精神病医生吧
But I guess that's why they call you a shrink
缩              小
你说我还有救吗  医生
Do you think there's hope for me, Doctor?
有救
Hope?
等秘方到我手上了
When I get my hands on that formula
你们就彻底没救了
there won't be any hope for any of you
对  我是说
Yeah, I mean
你马上就能治好了
you'll be cured in no time
好
Good
先从简单的训练开始
Let's start with a simple exercise
要开合跳吗
Jumping jacks?
我要你闭上双眼
I want you to close your eyes
闭紧点
Tighter
太紧了
Too tight
跟我说你看到了什么
Now, tell me what you see
我看到巨型蟹黄堡
I see giant Krabby Patties
很好
Good
蟹黄堡的成分是什么
And what are they made of?
憎恶
Hatred
不对  我是说食材
No, I mean ingredients
到底有什么破食材
What are the stinking ingredients?
蟹黄堡来抓我了
They're coming for me
不要
No
别过来
Stay back
等等  你哪来的钢琴
Wait, where'd you get that piano?
试试别的疗法
We're trying something else
我会说一个词  你要说出
I'm going to say a word, and I want you to say
你最先想到的第一个词
the first word that pops into your head
准备好了吗
Ready?
我准备好了
I'm ready
工作
Work
锅铲
Spatula
面包
Bun
你说的词得跟我不一样才行
See, the key is to say something
different than what I say
好吧  明白
Okay, I got it
土豆
Potato
马铃薯
Po-tah-to
番茄
Tomato
西红柿
To-mah-to
我放了点卡片  卡片上面写了点词
I've laid out some words on cards here
都是常见的厨房食材
These words are common kitchen ingredients
你要什么顺序  就按那顺序排
I want you to arrange them in any order you choose
可能会排成诗歌  或者秘方
It could be a poem or a secret formula
不知道
I don't know--
没错
Yes
秘方  很好
A secret formula, good
就排这个
Let's do that
你害我有点紧张了
You're making me nervous
好吧
Okay
那我就坐这了
I'll be over here, then
我排完了
I'm finished
我排成了钢琴
I arranged them into a piano
由于你的心智
Since your mind
目前为止都对各种精神疗法有抗性
has been resistant to every mental technique so far
我就只好采取
I'm forced to resort
我手上最强大的疗法来治疗你了
to my most powerful method of curing you
纤维吗
Fiber?
不对
No
催眠
Hypnosis
Hypnosis?
眼睛盯着这只表
Now, keep your eyes on this watch
等我数到三  你就会沉睡
When I count to three, you will fall into a deep sleep
一
One
二
two
三
three
居然奏效了
I can't believe it worked
等我打了响指
Now, when I snap my fingers
你就会醒来  把秘方全告诉我
you will awake and tell me the formula
醒醒
Wake up
还有什么声音又吵又讨厌
What else is loud and obnoxious?
你怎么就是不醒过来
Why won't you wake up?
这是哪里
Where am I?
海绵宝宝  听说你大脑不舒服
Hey, SpongeBob, I heard your brain was sick
所以我给你带了这个披萨饼干
so I brought you this cookie pizza
真谢谢你
Gee, thanks
还有巧克力奶给你
And here's some chocolate milk
风味乳饮料之王
The king of flavored dairy drinks
蟹黄堡啊
Oh, Krabby Patty
真高兴我们又是朋友了
I'm so glad we're friends again
别忘了  海绵宝宝
Just remember, SpongeBob
我一直都与你同在
I'll always be with you
就在这里
right here
我心里吗
In my heart?
其实是动脉
Actually, in your arteries
麻烦快点醒过来
Now, do me a favor and wake up
醒醒
Wake up
成功了
It worked
我康复了
I'm cured
可秘方怎么办
But what about the formula?
你说得对
You're right
我得回去工作了
I better get back to work
谢谢帮忙  医生
Thanks for everything, Doc
不对
No
刚刚骗你的
It's a lie
治疗没成功
Therapy doesn't really work
你还病着呢
You're still sick
病得可重了
Very, very sick
真高兴能看到你脑子恢复了  小子
Good to see your brain's all fixed, boy
对啊  原来我睡一觉就没事了
Yeah, I just needed some sleep is all
我能保证  再也不用24小时营业了
Well, I can safely say, no more 24-hour shifts
因为23小时就够了
'cause 23 hours'll be plenty
蟹老板啊
Mr. Krab
我没开玩笑
No, seriously
给我继续工作
Get back to work
虚有其表
分镜总监
编剧
翻译: 1440kHz
技术总监
动画总监
制片指导
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
蟹堡王
小心
Easy
完美
Perfection
五号餐做好了没  海绵宝宝
Is number five's order ready yet, SpongeBob?
再等一下  章鱼哥
Just a second, Squidward
蟹黄堡
Well, Krabby Patty
你现在该走了
it's time for you to go now
你长大得好快
You grew up so fast
我
I
我答应过自己不会这样的
I promised myself I wouldn't do this
你拿走吧  章鱼哥
Just take it, Squidward
快拿走
Take it away
烦死了
Oh, brother
此处点餐
五号
Number five
就是我
That's me
我要赞美厨子
My compliments to the chef
不会吧
Hello?
这是什么
What's this?
快出来  小子
Come out here, boy
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs?
别吵  小子
Hush, boy
不然会泄露我藏宝洞的位置
Or you'll give away your location of me hidey hole
藏宝洞是什么
What's a hidey hole?
是我藏宝的地方
It's where I hide me treasure
接着
Catch
快把宝箱搬去我办公室  小子
Let's get that chest to me office, boy, pronto
里面有什么
What's in this thing?
宝藏吗
Treasure?
算是财宝吧
A treasure trove of sorts
这是我的回忆箱
It's me memory chest
我海军服役时传下来的
from my years in the navy
干嘛要挖海军回忆箱
Why'd you dig up your navy chest, sir?
我跟我的战友要开战友会了
Well, me navy buddies and I are having a reunion
我要穿回我的旧制服
I wanted to wear me old uniform
你有好多好酷的海军玩意儿
Look at all your cool navy stuff
那是什么
What's that?
啊
Arrgh
是我第一个纹身
It's me first tattoo
漂亮
Neat
这是我的男子汉雄壮奖杯
And this is me manly toughness trophy
你怎么赢来的
How'd you win that?
当上强人中的强人就赢了
By being the toughest of the tough
那几位是谁
Who are those guys?
我的船友
Me shipmates
最强大的航海帮派
The toughest bunch to ever sail the briny deep
有老铁眼
There's old Iron Eye
络腮胡  我
and Mutton Chop, me
鱼雷肚
Torpedo Belly
还有锁齿琼斯
and Lockjaw Jones
你有酷外号吗  蟹老板
Did you have a cool nickname, Mr. Krabs?
那当然了
Of course
我曾经是铁甲金钟罩
I was old Armor Abs Krabs
曾经是
You were?
什么意思
What do you mean?
你当年瘦多了
Well, I guess you were thinner back then
是吗
Really?
这是我的海军学员制服
This is me navy cadet uniform
准备好把话收回去
Prepare to eat your words
因为我体重根本没增
'cause I haven't put on more
超过
than a
好几
couple of
磅
pounds
好吧  我是肥了点
Okay, maybe I'm a bit bigger
但还是强人中的强人
but I'm still the toughest of the tough
来啊  小子
Go ahead, lad
快打一拳
give 'em a punch
你要我打你肚子吗
You want me to punch you in the stomach?
不是打肚子  小子
Not in the stomach, lad
打铁甲金钟罩
in me armor abs
我整只手臂都碎了
My entire arm disintegrated
宝刀未老啊
I still got it
乖乖去打理工作环境吧
Be a good lad, go get your station in shipshape
让我这个老水手回味往日回忆
and leave an old sea dog to revel in his memories
遵命  老板
Aye, aye, sir
好了
All right
来把这里打理好吧
Let's get this place shipshape
你们几个  别到处闹腾了
You men, stop playing around
土豆
前往战斗位置
To battle stations
薯条
全体成员
All hands on deck
一定要有浓厚风味
That calls for full flavor
番茄酱芥末酱位于左舷前方
Ketchup and mustard off the port bow
一份蟹黄堡准备启航了
One Krabby Patty ready to set sail
不要
No
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
Mr. Krabs?
在吗
Hello?
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs?
你没事吧
You all right?
你困了吗
Are you sleepy?
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
闻不出他脉搏
I don't smell his pulse
什么动静
What's that?
有谁在那
Is somebody there?
别看我
Don't look at me
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
离我远点
Leave me be
你还活着
You're alive
而且
And
没穿衣服
naked
没错
It's true
我蜕皮了
I've molted
什么是蜕皮
What's "molted"?
就是螃蟹长太胖的话
It's when a crab gets too fat--
就会
well--
套不进壳里
outgrows his shell
壳会脱落
It falls off
铁甲金钟罩可不能这样到战友会露面
Armor Abs Krabs can't show up at the reunion like this
全身粉嫩嫩软绵绵  算不上雄壮
All pink and soft and unmanly
浑身赘肉  没一点腹肌
I'm all flab and no ab
真见鬼
Barnacles
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
抱歉刚刚爆粗口了  蟹老板
Sorry about the foul language, Mr. Krabs
你表现完完全全就是虚有其表
but you're acting like
there never was a man in that shell
蟹老板参军那会儿可是无所畏惧的啊
The Krabs of his navy days was fearless
绝不会被丢壳这种小事拖累
He wouldn't let something as insignificant
as a missing shell slow him down
没错
Yeah
你样子又笨又粉又肉的又有什么关系
Who cares how silly, pink and fleshy you look?
更何况你又手无缚鸡之力  又弱又废
How non-threatening, limp, and soggy you are
而且
How
我再也没法出门了
I can't go anywhere ever again
傻子破烂
Stupid, no good
里面好黑啊
It sure is dark in here
快看  蟹老板
Look, Mr. Krabs--
我变成你了
I'm you
海绵宝宝  你真是个天才
SpongeBob, you're a genius
真高兴你懂我意思了
Well, I'm glad you got my point
外表不重要
It's not about what's on the outside
内心才重要
It's what's on the inside
不对  你个白痴
No, you barnacle brain
我说的不是你的扯淡比喻
Not your silly metaphor
你  进我壳里
you, in me shell
让我想到办法了
It gives me an idea
你可以去战友会假装成我
You can go to the reunion and pretend to be me
我可以当海军战友了
I get to be a navy buddy?
当然你得先花点时间
Of course you'll need some time
把我性格学得像一点
to approximate me personality
那简单
That'll be a snap
我跟章鱼哥
Squidward and I
有好多年都背着你偷偷学你呢
have been doing it behind your back for years
好  看看你学得怎么样
All right, show me what you got
快看我
Look at me
我是蟹老板
I'm Mr. Krabs
我爱钱
I love money
还算可以
Say, that ain't half bad
我曾经赢过一次马拉松
I once won a marathon
因为终点线那边有人掉了一毛钱
because someone dropped a penny at the finish line
简直就是我
That's me
我每晚都给钱包盖被子
Every night, I tuck me wallet in
还给它讲睡前故事
and tell it a bedtime story
晚安  小包包
Good night, wallety
好好好  我知道你学得很像了
Yeah, okay, I get the point
你说什么
What's that you say?
我女儿珍珍要动手术吗
Me daughter Pearl needs an operation?
我亲自去动  这样省钱
I'll do it meself and save a nickel
可以了  海绵宝宝
That'll do, SpongeBob
裤头村大会堂
欢迎海军战友
那就试试
Well, here goes
从来没见过这么多雄壮的海军
I've never seen so many manly naval men
多强悍  多勇敢
So tough, so brave
多
so
欢迎海军战友
聪明
clever
我是他们的一员
And I'm one of them
你才不是
No, you're not
别给我搞砸了  海绵宝宝
Don't blow this for me, SpongeBob
我不会让你失望的  老板
I won't let you down, sir
铁甲金钟罩
Armor Abs Krabs
快跟战友一起来干杯
come join your old naval buddies in a toast
来了
Coming
我干了什么好事
What have I done?
就让派对号巨轮在这里抛锚吧
Okay, boys, let the S.S. Party drop anchor right here
都怪我先前乱来
I've created a monster
来点烈酒
Here's some grog
你还是很喜欢菠萝  对吧
You still like pineapple, right?
何止喜欢菠萝
Like pineapple?
我家就是菠萝
I live in one
老螃蟹还是一样雄壮
That old Krabs is as manly as ever
真不敢相信
I don't believe it
海绵宝宝居然成功了
SpongeBob is pulling it off
铁甲金钟罩  我老铁眼
Hey, Armor Abs, old Iron Eye here
可恨不得想打下你的传奇大肚了
has been itching to punch your legendary gut
觉得自己够雄壮就来啊
Well, if you think you're man enough
大事不妙了
This could be bad
发射鱼雷
Fire the torpedo
怎么样啊  老螃蟹
What do you say, Krabs?
跟从前一个样
Just like old times
一颗牙
A tooth?
好几颗牙
Teeth
这才叫雄壮
Now, that's manly
他做到了
He did it
好了  我的水兵们
All right, me swabbies
现在要来颁发男子汉雄壮奖杯
it's time to award the trophy of manly toughness
获奖者久经岁月  依然气势磅礴
to a man whose toughness has stood the test of time
他就是铁甲金钟罩  尤金蟹
That man is Eugene Armor Abs Krabs
上来吧  老螃蟹
Come up here, Krabs
这就是我一生中最美好的夜晚
This is the best night of me life
我的战友依然觉得我很雄壮
Me naval buddies still think I'm manly
铁甲金钟罩
Armor Abs
而且还不必自惭形秽了
And I didn't have to shame myself
感谢大家让我得奖
Thanks for the trophy, everybody
致辞
Speech
我
I
说几句话
Say something
我来给大家讲个雄壮小故事
Let me spin you a manly yarn
真棒
Attaboy
我那时在水母田
So there I was, in Jellyfish Fields
我完蛋了
I'm doomed
泡泡水已经少得可怜了
Me supply of bubble soap was dangerously low
正当我吹出了最后一个泡泡
And as I blew my last bubble
他刚刚说水母田吗
Did he say Jellyfish Fields?
吹泡泡
Blowing bubbles?
你在水母田干什么了
What were you doing in Jellyfish Fields?
当然是捉水母啊
Why, jellyfishing, of course
有电话找蟹老板
Phone call for Mr. Krabs
快下台
Get off the stage
那个  我得走了
Well, I gotta go
谢了
Thanks
你这是想去哪
Where do you think you're going?
众所周知
Everybody knows
铁甲金钟罩有两件事绝对不会做
there's two things old Armor Abs Krabs would never do
完了
Oh, no
第一件就是花钱
Number one is spend a penny
第二件就是说走就走
And the other one is leave
没给鱼雷肚耍点你的招牌肚皮硬碰硬
without giving old Torpedo Belly
one of your world-famous steely belly butts
还以为你看穿我技俩了
I thought you'd seen through my ruse
我是说  啊
I mean, arrgh
你们该不会以为
You didn't think
我只来领男子汉雄壮奖杯就走吧
I was just gonna collect
this here trophy of manly toughness
我可要另外提醒你们这些弱者
without reminding yous lily-livers
打一开始为什么我得奖了  你们却没得
why you give it to me in the first place?
快来硬碰硬吧
Let's have at it
别放水
No holding back
使出全力
Give it your all
我不敢看
I can't watch
铁甲金钟罩
Armor Abs?
那个
Well, uh
我我我我我我
I-I-I-I-I-I
我就先拿走我的男子汉雄壮奖杯
I guess I'll just take my manly toughness trophy
回家去吧
and head home now
男子汉村再见  小子
See you around Manville, boys
好汉
men
不要
No
他不是尤金蟹
He's not Eugene Krabs
我才是
I am
大家听我说
All right, lads
好好看看
Take a good look
这个才是我
This is who I am
我蜕了壳  变得很
I've molted me shell and I'm
脆弱
vulnerable
但我绝不会吹泡泡又捉水母
But I'm certainly no bubble-blowing jellyfisher
无意冒犯  海绵宝宝
No offense, SpongeBob
没放心上  蟹老板
None taken, Mr. Krabs
走了  小子
Come on, lad
回去吧
Let's go home
等一下
Wait a minute
有东西你忘带了
You've forgotten something
我不明白
I don't understand
承认你失去了自己的壳
Admitting you lost your shell
是我见过最强悍的事了
was the toughest thing I've ever seen
还有
And, uh
我有话要坦白
I have a confession
这些是假的
These are fake
什么
What?
看这边
Over here
你也是吗  鱼雷肚
You too, Torpedo Belly?
其实鱼雷很久以前就取出来了
Actually, I had my torpedo removed long ago
这牙已经不是我参军当年的牙了
And these aren't the same choppers
that I had in the navy
我的铁眼其实是塑料装饰板做的
My iron eye is actually made of Formica
你看看  蟹老板
Look at that, Mr. Krabs
你战友都有见不得人的小秘密
Your navy buddies all had something to hide
对啊  太可悲了
Yeah, poor suckers
起码我壳还会再长回来
At least my shell will grow back